mathematainment.com 2017-01-26

# PrivacyPolicy

**“We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties”**

Mathematainment takes your privacy very seriously. We ask that you read this privacy policy carefully as it contains important information about what to expect when we collect personal information about you and how we will use your personal data. All personal information provided to us or gathered by us is kept and administered by [Mathematainment Limited at Eighth Floor, 6 New Street Square, New Fetter Lane, London, United Kingdom EC4A 3AQ] [Mathematainment Limited is part of the Mathematainment group of companies, including (details).]

This policy applies to information we collect about the following people:

  * visitors to our website;

  * users of any Mathematainment software, including Mathematainment Mobile Applications, which may be released from time to time;

  * our members (including all people who register for our services);

  * people who offer materials for sale through any Mathematainment platform;

  * people who purchase and/or download materials from Mathematainment platforms;

  * users of Mathematainment materials; and

  * people who sign up to receive emails from Mathematainment (including to mailing lists).

The activities described above are the “User Activites” referred to in this privacy policy.

**1\. The information we collect about you:**

When you do the User Activities, we collect all or some of the following personal information from you (depending on the nature of the User Activity):

  * your name;

  * your account details, including your username and password and any information you put into your Mathematainment user profile;

  * information you give us (or use to contact us) such as your account settings, your postal address, email address, and telephone number; 

  * payment and accounts information such as your credit or debit card number and expiry date, details of sales made of materials you have uploaded, and your account details with third party web sites such as PayPal necessary to make sure that your payments are dealt with appropriately; and

  * automatic data including technical information (such as your IP address, operating system, device type and time zone details), information about your connection to Mathematainment (such as the URL you are visiting, how you arrived at the URL, browser type and method of leaving your Mathematainment session), and session information (such as cookie number, details of activity on our web site, download data and details of any errors you may encounter); and

  * content information such as the information in your library lists, materials you viewed or searched for, content of any files you provide for distribution through Mathematainment platforms, and metadata associated with those files.

The specific information will in some cases depend on your own device settings and the way in which you use Mathematainment. For example, where you use mobile apps developed by Mathematainment or its agents and have enabled location services, automatic data may include information about your location, and using a mobile device may include sending a unique identifier for your device. Most browsers and mobile devices allow you to control the information that is sent automatically.

Occasionally we may receive information about you from other sources which we will add to the information which we already hold about you and others in order to help us customise your Mathematainment experience, display relevant offers and recommend materials you may be interest in.

**2\. How we will use the information about you:**

We gather this information to allow us to process your registration, process any orders you may make, process orders for content you have sold through Mathematainment platforms, provide you with Mathematainment products and ensure that you can use content downloaded through Mathematainment effectively. The information is then used by us (or companies we work with) to and to communicate with you, provide Mathematainment products and services in general, and provide you with accounting and licence details as required. If you agree, we may also contact you about other products and services we think may be of interest to you.

Mathematainment is a community resource and some information you provide is designed to be made public and this will be visible publicly online. This includes information such as your username, public profile data, comments and reviews you leave on the Mathematainment platform, and any public libraries and lists that you create.

We may also use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help us to develop our website and our services. We may also provide such aggregate information to third parties, but these statistics will never include any information that can be used to identify you or any payment or financial details.

From time to time we may provide your information to third parties including our customer service agencies for research and analysis purposes so that we can monitor and improve our services. We or our agents and sub-contractors may contact you to ask you for your feedback and comments on Mathematainment, but you will always be free to ignore any requests.

**3\. Marketing:**

We [and our group companies] may also wish to provide you with information about special features of our website or any other service or products we think may be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information or would like to control any other aspects of how we notify and contact you, please update your account details [insert relevant link]. We may also want to provide you with related information from third parties we think may be of interest to you, which can also be cotrolled via your account settings. If you agree to us providing you with marketing information, you can always opt out at a later date by changing your account settings.

We may also provide your information to carefully selected third parties whose products or services we believe may be of interest to you. If you do not wish us to disclose your information in this way, that too can be altered in the same account settings page. We may also in some cases offer co-branded products and services, which may include sharing information with those companies that we work with. In such cases, any information shared will be kept to a minimum and will always be anonymous.

**4\. Our use of cookies and other information-gathering technologies:**

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behaviour information. The information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. For further information about cookies visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org. You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases some of our website features may not function if you remove cookies from your browser. This may be important for some key features of the Mathematainment service, such as remembering your login to Mathematainment web sites and making sure you are able to view and re-download content purchased through our services. 

**5\. How we protect your information:**

We have put in place the following security procedures and technical and organisational measures to safeguard your personal information: **[firewall, regular virus and malware scans, and appropriate SSL certification].**

We will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal information. However, you should be aware that the use of the Internet is not entirely secure and for this reason we cannot guarantee the security or integrity of any personal information which is transferred from you or to you via the Internet. 

**6\. Overseas and other transfers:**

The information you provide may be transferred to countries outside the European Economic Area (‘EEA’) that do not have similar protections in place regarding your data and restrictions on its use as set out in this policy. However, we will take steps to ensure adequate protections are in place to ensure the security of your information. The EEA comprises the EU member states plus Norway, Iceland and Liechtenstein. By submitting your information you consent to these transfers for the purposes specified above. Examples of where information may be transferred abroad is to other Mathematainment group companies to ensure that you are able to access your materials from any international Mathematainment platform, or where content sellers are located internationally. In these cases information will always be anonymous or safeguarded by security measures similar to those described above. By using Mathematainment services you consent to such information being provided in this way under the Data Protection Act 1998 Schedule 4.

If Mathematainment’s business is sold or integrated with another business your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the business.

**7\. Access to your information and updating and correcting your information:**

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please send a letter to Mathematainment Limited Data Protection at Eighth Floor, 6 New Street Square, New Fetter Lane, London, United Kingdom EC4A 3AQ or send an email to [info@mathematainment.com](mailto:info@mathematainment.com) with “Data Protection Request” in the subject field. We may make a small charge for this service. We want to ensure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. If any of the information that you have provided to us changes, for example if you change your email address, name or payment details, or if you wish to cancel your registration, please let us know the correct details by updating your account Mathematainment Limited Data Protection at Eighth Floor, 6 New Street Square, New Fetter Lane, London, United Kingdom EC4A 3AQ or send an email to [info@mathematainment.com](mailto:info@mathematainment.com) with “Update to personal information” in the subject field.. You may ask us, or we may ask you, to correct information you or we think is inaccurate, and you may also ask us to remove information which is inaccurate.

**8\. Your consent:**

By submitting your personal information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy.

**9\. Changes to privacy policy:**

As part of our responsibility to you we keep our privacy policy under regular review. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times.

**10 How to contact Mathematainment:**

We welcome your views about our website and our privacy policy. If you would like to contact us with any queries or comments please send an email to [info@mathematainment.com](mailto:info@mathematainment.com) or send a letter to Mathematainment Limited Data Protection at Eighth Floor, 6 New Street Square, New Fetter Lane, London, United Kingdom EC4A 3AQ.

**11\. Links to other websites:**

Our website contains links to other websites. Because of the nature of the internet, we cannot be responsible for third party content or information. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.
